(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-05T23:16:38.821340",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
開演までしばらくお待ちください
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のお客様へ
Notice to Visitors
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration Open Now!
ローソンにお越しのみなさん！
To everyone visiting Lawson!
2026年01月
January 2026
ローソンキャンペーン実施決定！
[Lawson Campaign Confirmed!]
今回はこの6人が登場！
Featuring these 6 members this time!
詳細は3/9(月)公開予定！
Details scheduled to be released on 3/9 (Mon)!
今年のバンダイブースも超スゴい！
This year's Bandai booth is super awesome too!
注目の新商品も初公開！
First-ever look at hot new products!
会場限定、スペシャルフォトブース！
Venue-exclusive Special Photo Booth!
限定カードももらえる！
You can also get limited cards!
来場してね！
Please come visit!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
Hey, I want to say thank you again and again,
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
and tell you right now.
さあ乗り込もう！ ridin' on dreams, yeah!
Come on, let's board! Ridin' on dreams, yeah!
Woah, oh~oh, woah, oh~oh
Hey! Hey! Yeah!
あぁ 小さな夢から
Ah, starting from a tiny dream,
想像できないような
it became a feeling
想いになったんだ
that I couldn't even imagine.
わくわく止まらない！
My excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we get lost,
絆が船になる
our bond becomes a ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety,
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
we can blow it all away!
果てない旅路を今
Right now on this endless journey,
漕いでる途中に出る困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be hardships as we row forward.
それも力に変えて
We'll turn even those into strength,
一組に進むんだよ！
and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't let this end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome even the rough waves.
“らしさ”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行こう！ ridin' on dreams
we'll keep going and going! Ridin' on dreams!
Woah, oh~oh, woah, oh~oh
Hey! Hey! Yeah!
急な風が僕らの
Even if a sudden gust of wind
行く先乱そうとも
tries to disrupt our path,
あの日誓ったんだ
we made a vow that day,
覚悟は揺るがない
our resolve will never waver.
「ちゃんとしなきゃ！」って背中
Saying 'I have to do this right!'
明日への橋になる
becomes a bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it even more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship,
どっから始まめたらいいかもがいて
struggling with where to even begin.
少しずつ輪になって見つけた
Bit by bit, forming a circle, we found
何にも代えられない夢だ
an irreplaceable dream.
未完成も愛して
Loving even our imperfections,
想いは一つだ
our feelings are one.
わずかな希望でも
Even with just a slender hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I will always...
馬鹿にされても信じたい！
Even if made fun of, I want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, 'thank you' isn't enough.
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
Hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there.
ねえ、夢では終われない
Hey, we can't let this end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome even the rough waves.
“らしく”輝いていたい
I want to shine in my own way.
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, meeting you...
ねえ、宝物だから
Hey, is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Holding hands and calling out to each other,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world with no map,
まだまだ行けるから！
we can still keep going!
ひとりじゃない
We are not alone.
何度でも立ち上がってさ
We'll stand back up as many times as it takes,
笑い合っていたい願いだって
and smile together—that's our wish.
みんなで、さあ！
Everyone, come on!
手を手を繋いで想像も超えて
Joining hands, exceeding all imagination,
まだまだ行こう！ ridin' on dreams
let's keep going! Ridin' on dreams!
Woah, oh~oh, woah, oh~oh
Hey! Hey! Yeah!
まもなく開演いたします
The concert will be starting soon.
ご来場のお客様へ
Notice for Visitors
事前登録受付中！
Pre-registration is now open!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there,
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
hey, I want to say thank you...
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
...again and again right now.
さあ乗り込もう！ Ridin' on dreams
Come on, let's climb aboard! Ridin' on dreams!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream...
想像できないような
...it grew into feelings...
想いになったんだ
...beyond anything we imagined.
わくわく止まらない！
This excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we lose our way...
絆が船になる
...our bonds will become our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety...
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
...we can blow it all away!
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey now,
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be hardships along the way.
それも力に変えて
We'll turn even those into strength...
一緒に進むんだよ！
...and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there,
ねえ、夢では終われない
hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves...
“らしく”輝いていたい
...and shine in our own true way!
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
...is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Taking each other's hands and calling out,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world without a map,
まだまだ行こう！ Ridin' on dreams
let's keep going! Ridin' on dreams!
急な風が僕らの
Even if sudden winds try to disrupt...
行く先乱そうとも
...the path we're taking,
あの日誓ったんだ
we made a vow that day...
覚悟は揺るがない
...and our resolve will never waver.
ちゃんとしなきゃ！って背中
Telling ourselves "Must do our best!"...
明日への橋になる
...becomes the bridge to tomorrow.
もっと大事にしなきゃね
We have to cherish it even more,
“あたりまえ”は無いから
because nothing is taken for granted.
小さな船から始まるストーリー
A story starting from a small ship,
どっから始めたらいいのかもがいて
struggling to figure out where to begin,
少しずつね輪になって見つけた
little by little coming together and finding...
何にも代えられない夢だ
...a dream that cannot be replaced!
未完成も愛して
Embracing even what's unfinished,
想いは一つだ
our feelings are as one.
わずかな希望でも
Even with just a tiny ray of hope,
僕と君でずっと
you and I, forever...
馬鹿にされても
even if people make fun of us,
信じたい！
...we want to believe!
ねえ、ありがとうじゃ足りない
Hey, "thank you" just isn't enough,
ねえ、想いが溢れちゃうんだよ
hey, my feelings are overflowing.
ずっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together forever!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there,
ねえ、夢では終われない
hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves...
“らしさ”輝いていたい
...and keep shining as myself!
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
...is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Taking each other's hands and calling out,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world without a map,
まだまだ行けるから！
because we can still go further!
ひとりじゃない
You are not alone,
何度でも立ち上がってさ
no matter how many times, we'll rise again...
笑い合っていたい
...and keep laughing together.
願いだってみんなで、さあ！
Even our wishes, everyone, come on!
手をつないで想像も超えて
Holding hands and going beyond imagination,
まだまだ行こう！ Ridin' on dreams
let's keep going! Ridin' on dreams!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there,
ねえ、ありがとうを何度も
hey, I want to say thank you...
今すぐに伝えたいんだ
...again and again right now.
さあ乗り込もう！ Ridin' on dreams
Come on, let's climb aboard! Ridin' on dreams!
あぁ小さな夢から
Ah, from a small dream...
想像できないような
...it grew into feelings...
想いになったんだ
...beyond anything we imagined.
わくわく止まらない！
This excitement won't stop!
何度迷ったって僕ら
No matter how many times we lose our way...
絆が船になる
...our bonds will become our ship.
ちょっとの不安だってさ
Even a little bit of anxiety...
吹き飛ばせちゃうんだよ
...we can blow it all away!
果てない旅路を今
On this endless journey now,
漕いでる途中に困難もあるでしょう
there will surely be hardships along the way.
それも力に変えて
We'll turn even those into strength...
一緒に進むんだよ！
...and move forward together!
ねえ、君がいたからだよ
Hey, it's because you were there,
ねえ、夢では終われない
hey, it can't end as just a dream.
荒波も乗り越えていこう
Let's overcome the rough waves...
“らしく”輝いていたい
...and shine in our own true way!
ねえ、君と会えたことが
Hey, being able to meet you...
ねえ、宝物だから
...is my greatest treasure.
手を取り合い声かけ合って
Taking each other's hands and calling out,
地図など無い未知の世界で
in an unknown world without a map,
まだまだ行こう！ Ridin' on dreams
let's keep going! Ridin' on dreams!
ホロリス各位！声出してけ〜！
To all Holo-fans! Make some noise~!
hololive 7th fes. Ridin' on Dreams
ハーモニー重ねた過去が
The past built on harmony
届くまで
Until it reaches you...
つたない願い描いては
As I drew my clumsy wishes,
ギコチナイと笑ってた
I used to laugh, calling myself awkward.
未来のそう あの日の続きを見よう
Let's look toward the future, continuing from that day.
手と手繋いで 風も着こなして
Hand in hand, riding with the wind,
扉を叩いて 連れて行くよ
I'll knock on the door and take you with me.
どんなこともきっと 一緒なら叶えていける
As long as we're together, we can make any dream come true.
La La La La 鳴り止まない 希望を乗せる
La La La La, carrying endless hope.
ほら ラーラーラー
Look, la-la-la...
聞こえてる (聞こえてる) 歌 (あー)
Can you hear it? (Can you hear it?) The song...
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony, words layered together
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond these vibrant days
いつしか君と響く 色付くストーリー
Before we know it, a story echoing and coloring with you
ハーモニー 結んだ夢が
Harmony, the dreams we bound together
空へ駆けていく きらめき乗せて
Soaring into the sky, carrying our sparkle
あなたへ
To you
届けるメロディ どこまでも
A melody delivered endlessly
何気ないことも思い出す
Remembering even the casual moments
一人じゃないよって深呼吸
Taking a deep breath, knowing I'm not alone
見たい景色 楽しむ魔法の言葉
Magical words to enjoy the scenery we want to see
一歩踏み出して ふと振り返って
Taking a step forward, suddenly looking back
また君を知って
Getting to know you once again
その度に ちょっと勇気出して
Every time, gathering a little courage
明日へ飛び込んでいけ
Diving into tomorrow
ラーラーラー 降り積もる道標はまだ
La-la-la, the signposts piling up are still...
ラーラーラー 覚えている 歌 (あー)
La-la-la, remembering the song...
ハーモニー 手を伸ばしたら
Harmony, if we reach out our hands
足跡に虹がかかる
A rainbow forms over our footsteps
解き放たれる 未完成なステージ
Unleashed upon this unfinished stage
ハーモニー 印した場所へ
Harmony, to the place we marked
運ぶ約束を 輝き乗せて
Carrying our promise, filled with radiance
世界へ
To the world
響いてメロディ いつまでも
Resonate, melody, forevermore
君と踏み出したあの一歩 あの瞬間が
That step I took with you, that very moment
宝物だって胸を張る 今
Proudly holding it as my treasure, right now
言い残せないまま
Without leaving anything unsaid
混ざり合う 僕らの声 ほら
Our voices blending together, look
聞こえてる (聞こえてる) 歌 (あー)
Can you hear it? (Can you hear it?) The song...
ハーモニー 重ねた言葉
Harmony, words layered together
鮮やかな日々の向こう
Beyond these vibrant days
ずっと君と 彩るストーリー
A story colored forever with you
ハーモニー 結んだ夢が
Harmony, the dreams we bound together
空へ駆けていく きらめき乗せて
Soaring into the sky, carrying our sparkle
あなたへ
To you
世界へ
To the world
愛のメロディ どこまでも
A melody of love, echoing endlessly
パレード パレード パレード 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! Keep on shining!
呼び合う声を合図に
Calling out to each other as our signal
パレード パレード パレード 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade! Let's go search!
スタートは何度だって
We can start over as many times as it takes
一筋の続く道
A single path stretching onward
ただ 始まりたくて走った
I ran simply wanting a fresh start
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Lit far off in the darkness
それは 眩しすぎた名前
That was a name far too dazzling
それは 優しすぎる思い出
Those were memories far too gentle
もっと 近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get closer
思いがけずすれ違った
Unexpectedly passing each other by
ほら 今 周りはこんなになった
Look, now our world has become like this
パレード パレード パレード 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade! Keep on shining!
悔しさも愛おしさも 連れておいで
Bring along both your regrets and affection
風 夢 羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りばかり
Filled with modest prayers
終わりなき兆し
Sign of an endless light...
君を見つけたこと
Finding you is something...
胸を張れるよ
I can be proud of.
ここから
From here,
これから
from now on,
Our bright parade, parade!
まだ 頼りない予感を
I'll sing of these...
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
uncertain feelings without any shame.
誰も解けない イマジナリー
An imaginary world no one can decode,
いつかまた逢える おまじない
a spell so we can meet again someday.
あの日 ゼロに始まった ストーリー
The story that started from zero that day...
数え切れない 言の葉
Countless words,
数えるような 想いじゃないさ
feelings that can't be counted up.
ほら 今 「僕等」を 一つと呼ぼう
Look, now let me call "us" as one!
Parade, Parade, Parade! 美しいんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It's so beautiful!
許し合える刹那 夜はきらめく
A fleeting moment of mutual forgiveness, the night sparkles!
雨、晴れ、カレイド またとない空
Rain, sunshine, kaleidoscope, a one-of-a-kind sky!
相応しい旅路とは 君と在ることさ
The right journey is being with you,
君と在ることなんだ
yes, being together with you.
「ただいま」を聞けば
When I hear "I'm back,"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
I shout "Welcome home!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that natural?
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! Shine bright!
暗がりを満たすのは 君だ 僕だ！
What fills the darkness is you and me!
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! Shine bright!
悔しさも 愛しさも 連れておいで
Bring along your regrets and your love!
風、夢、羽 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can fly high!
ささやかな祈りは 光 終わりなき兆し
Modest prayers become light, signs of an endless future,
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
diving in with you is a wonderful start!
ここから
From here,
これから
from now on,
Our bright parade, parade!
4th Fes! ステージ1も盛り上がっていきましょう！
4th Fes! Let's get hyped for Stage 1 as well!
ステージ1 最初から飛ばしていくぞー！
Let's go full speed right from the start of Stage 1!
Hits on, sound on, darling, what's the matter?
ゾロ目出目揃った時 見えたでしょ？
When the matching dice landed, you saw it, right?
高鳴る声 Outsmart myself, fake, authentic, show
Throbbing voice, outsmart myself, fake, authentic show.
豪快 Lucky Dollars 熱狂
Spectacular Lucky Dollars, pure excitement.
Tell 'em I win ここでは一兆 天下無双
Tell 'em I win, worth a trillion here, second to none!
Break a bank, get the dough, let somebody hit the floor
振りかざした刀口 一投勝負
Brandishing a blade in a single throw showdown,
見せてあげる 完膚なきまでの勝利を
I'll show you an absolute, total victory.
一つ、合図で決まる勝敗
First, the outcome decided by a single signal,
この世界中を手中に収めるまで
until I hold this entire world in my hands!
Drawing the knife, my conviction, cold as ice, sell my soul to...
You know I gotcha!
You know everybody panics, see my eyes, what's the magic?
少年場 熱狂 枠組み破るアティチュード
Crucial moment, craze, an attitude breaking boundaries.
ハイローでいこうかい 参列 窮地で踊り明かそう
Highs and lows, let me go in, line up, let's dance all night through the pinch!
High stakes, I take it home
You're lucky, I think I'm gonna get ya
Break down
ハイヒール チェンジ 安定感なんて性分？
High heels change, is stability in my nature?
吹っ飛ばしていけ Highway, 轟け My name!
Blow past on the highway, roar my name!
くだらん邪魔立て 歓声 集中に落とすわ
Nonsensical interference, cheers, I'll bring them down with focus.
容赦一切ない カラクリ 洗いざらいに
Unforgiving tricks, exposed all out,
滾るハイを求め 遊び尽くすの
seeking a surging high, playing it out to the end!
なんだかんだ方面渋滞
Traffic jam in all directions, one way or another
To ABC underline
そう言う神 in a bind
So-called gods in a bind
That's why I catch ya!
You know everybody panic
審判も言わばマジ
Even the judges are for real, so to speak
安全調調も B-class
Even the safety pitch is B-class
ひとまずはいわば
For now, so to speak...
大好き あんなドラマチック
I love it, something so dramatic
そう一口味わってから最後
So after taking just one bite, at the end
審判もマジで
Even the judges are serious
Child's play, I take it home
勝者の行く末 待つは滅亡
What awaits the victor's future is ruin
勝負の行方は神のみぞ知る
The outcome of the match is known only to God
So pomp and grace like a king with a crown
I'm the princess in the town
This game's only just begun
Get lucky, I think I'm gonna...
溢れる欲望 導くままに 溺れず降臨する私
Guided by overflowing desires, I descend without drowning
Jackpot, jackpot, jackpot, set! I embody a happy win, I make everybody gain!
Look at the crowd! High on me, going mad!
狂乱に酔いしれ 踊り狂うのが宿命
Drunk on frenzy, dancing wildly is my destiny
審判もマジで I will get, get down
Even the judges are serious, I will get, get down
Such a class, such a show of ally, I'm getting lucky tonight
Get, get down, watch the power
思うままにリターンを得る 豪快な勝利を Take it home
Gaining returns as I please, taking home a spectacular victory
幕張ー！
Makuhari~!
Showtime! 一緒に歌い… Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU Yeah!
Showtime! Sing together... Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU Yeah!
You and I, BAU! 魔界乃番犬 Sisters!
You and I, BAU! Demon Realm Guard Dog Sisters!
もっと近くで！
Closer!
ここ！ここ！ここ！ここ！
Here! Here! Here! Here!
BAU BAU BAU BAU!
心も体もフワモコで 気持ちごと浮くことあるけど
Heart and body feeling fluffy and soft, sometimes our feelings float away
吠えれば魔界の番犬で あなたの笑顔を守りたいよ
But when we bark, we're the Demon Realm guard dogs who want to protect your smile!
ここ！ここ！ここ！ここ！
Here! Here! Here! Here!
イタズラ大好きフェローモコ お散歩大好きリードはいらんー！
Mischief-loving PeroMoco! Loves walks, no leash needed~!
どこへでもフワモコついていくから フワモコ達も連れて行って
FuwaMoco will follow you anywhere, so take the FuwaMocos along too!
2人で吠える！
We bark together!
Showtime! 一緒に歌い… Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU!
Showtime! Sing together... Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU!
生涯 Sing with you 大切な Showtime Forever More!
Lifetime, Sing with you! Precious Showtime Forever More!
Showtime! 一緒に歌い… Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU Yeah!
Showtime! Sing together... Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU Yeah!
You and I, BAU! 魔界乃番犬 Sisters!
You and I, BAU! Demon Realm Guard Dog Sisters!
BAU! BAU! BAU! BAU!
昔々おりの中で ワクワクドキドキ抑えられ
Once upon a time inside a cage, holding back exciting thrills...
走り出しそうになっちゃって 大脱走の大絶叫タイム！
Almost bursting into a run, a great escape of loud shouting time!
ゴールを目指して足は止まらない
Aiming for the goal, our feet won't stop
笑顔一番 楽しさ止まらない
Smiles are number one, the fun won't stop
今はまだまだ怖がりだけど 2人の絆は強いから
We're still a bit scared right now, but the bond between us two is strong
絶対挫けない！
We will never give up!
だからいつだって 歌っていくー！
So we'll keep on singing anytime~!
Lifetime Showtime! Let's go!
一生 Showtime! One with you! どんな大変だって構わない
Lifetime Showtime! One with you! No matter how tough, we don't care
いつだって いつだって Lifetime Showtime Everyday BAU BAU Yeah!
Always, always! Lifetime Showtime Everyday BAU BAU Yeah!
2人は Happy Lucky Puppy Sisters!
The two of us are Happy Lucky Puppy Sisters!
All together! フワモコ BAU BAU! Everybody BAU BAU!
All together! FuwaMoco BAU BAU! Everybody BAU BAU!
BAU BAU BAU BAU! Everybody BAU BAU!
ドメドメ NONO Don't touch ear!
No-no, NO NO, Don't touch ears!
モフモフ NONO Don't touch tail!
Fluffy NONO, Don't touch tails!
チワワじゃないよ フワワだよ BAU!
I'm not a Chihuahua, I'm Fuwawa, BAU!
パピヨンじゃないよ モココだよ BAU!
I'm not a Papillon, I'm Mococo, BAU!
魔界の番犬 Sisters BAU!
Demon Realm Guard Dog Sisters, BAU!
Take it away, フワモコー！
Take it away, FuwaMoco~!
2人分の…
For the two of us...
夢を掛け合わせたら
If we combine our dreams...
目が覚めてしまうほどの
So amazing it wakes you right up,
夢限大になっちゃう！
It becomes infinitely huge!
たくさんあって
There are so many...
叶えきれないかもだけど
We might not be able to grant them all, but
ずっとチャレンジできるー！
We can keep on challenging forever!
一緒だから！
Because we're together!
一生 Showtime! 一緒に歌い… ふふっ 一生 Showtime! 一緒に歌い… ふふっ
Lifetime Showtime! Sing together... Fu-fu! Lifetime Showtime! Sing together... Fu-fu!
一生 Showtime! 一緒にいたいよ フワフワ モコモコ 包まれて 君の笑顔を守りたい 一番のお願い
Lifetime Showtime! I want to be together! Wrapped up in Fuwa-Fuwa Moco-Moco, I want to protect your smile, that's my number one wish!
一生 Showtime! 一緒にいたい… Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU!
Lifetime Showtime! Want to be together... Lifetime Showtime Anytime BAU BAU!
生涯 Sing with you 大切な Showtime Forever More! 一生 Showtime!
Lifetime, Sing with you! Precious Showtime Forever More! Lifetime Showtime!
Share the love, light the night
Showtime anytime
Go go ahead
Together with Ruffians
Happy puppy everyday
Let's go BAU!
FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO BAU!
ありがとうー！
Thank you!
FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO BAU BAU FUWA MOCO FUWA MOCO BAU!
BAU!
誰がなんと言おうと
No matter what anyone says,
今日はクリスマス...
today is Christmas...
これは...
This is...
キミとの...
a story of...
約束の物語...
a promise with you...
ペコチキン、いかがペコか〜！？
How about some Peko Chicken, peko~!?
ジューシーバリバリ ジューシーバリバリ
Juicy and crispy, juicy and crispy!
いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さぁさぁ今日も元気に焼いて焼いて焼いちゃって
Come on, today again, lively frying, frying, frying away!
ぼっち様 幹事様 お一人飛んでパーティー様
For solo guests, party planners, lone flyers, and party crowds!
どうでしょう一つ ペコチキン
How about one Peko Chicken?
えっさほいさ 焼き上げろ
Heave-ho, heave-ho, fry it up!
あっちゅーまに行列だ
In no time, there's a long line!
レジの向こう お腹空腹人 待たせてsorry
Hungry people beyond the register, sorry for making you wait!
てんやわんやしちゃうケド
It gets super chaotic, but...
キチンとね仕上げるぞ
I'll prepare it properly!
込める秘伝のスパイス
Infused with secret spices,
ラブアンドピース
Love and Peace!
美味しくなれなれ
Become delicious, delicious...
唱えて
Chant it!
じっくりじっくり こんがりこんがり
Slowly, slowly, deep golden brown...
ギラっとカラっと輝いて
Shining bright, crispy and golden!
ほかほか シャキーン！変身だ！
Piping hot, *shing*! Time to transform!
お待たせペコ！喰らえ！
Sorry to keep you waiting, peko! Dig in!
やめらんねーよ やめらんねーよ ペコチキン
Can't stop, can't stop eating Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ とんでもねーよ ペコチキン
Incredible, incredible Peko Chicken!
パリっとジュワっとホロッと たっぷりアツアツ
Crisp, juicy, tender, piping hot!
ほらお一つどうでしょう？
Here, how about having one?
やめらんねーな やめらんねーな ペコチキン
Just can't stop, just can't stop eating Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーな とんでもねーな ペコチキン
So incredible, so incredible Peko Chicken!
ガブっとバリっとクラっと にんまりぺろり
Chomp, crunch, dizzy with delight, grinning as I devour it!
おかしくなっちゃう美味しさ
A deliciousness that drives you wild!
一丁お届け
Delivering one order!
絶対お届け
Definitely delivering!
お待たせペコ！
Sorry to keep you waiting, peko!
冷めたらチンしてペコチキン
If it gets cold, pop Peko Chicken in the microwave!
あーあー、この度はご来店いただき、誠に、誠にありがとうございます。
Ah- ah-, thank you so much, truly so much for visiting us today.
本日も元気に焼いておりますのは、肉汁脳汁たっぷり！ペコチキンでございます。
What we're actively frying up today is overflowing with meat juice and brain juice! Peko Chicken!
「熱く、こんがり、冷まさない」をモットーに、ジューシーバリバリ、ジューシーバリバリ取り揃えております。
With our motto "Hot, golden, never let it cool down," we offer plenty of juicy, crispy options!
皆様の日頃のご愛顧に感謝を込めて、ただいまよりチキンフィーバータイム突入とさせていただきます。
To express our gratitude for your continued support, we are now entering Chicken Fever Time!
それでは、お呼び出しを申し上げます！
Now, let us call out to our customers!
アツアツチキンのお客様〜？
Customers who want piping hot chicken~?
お一人ぼっちのお客様〜？
Customers who are all by themselves~?
自称パーティーピーポーのお客様〜？
Customers who claim to be party people~?
骨なしチキンのお客様〜？
Customers ordering boneless chicken~?
ハニーシロップラードショットのお客様〜？
Customers ordering honey syrup lard shots~?
ニクアブラマシマシカラメのお客様〜？
Customers ordering extra meat, extra fat, extra flavor~?
限界突破完凸希望のお客様〜？
Customers wishing for max limit break~?
お腹ペコペコのお客様〜？
Customers who are super hungry~?
聖なる夜には？
On this holy night?
どこでも向かうよ ペコチキン
I'll head anywhere, Peko Chicken!
遅くなってごめんね
Sorry for being late,
やっと言えた世界で
in a world where I could finally say it.
冷えた孤独を温めてあげる
I'll warm up your cold loneliness.
一人じゃないよもう
You're not alone anymore.
冷めた食卓に彩りを
Bringing color to a cold dining table.
それが聖なるペコチキン！
That is the holy Peko Chicken!
だからだから
Therefore, therefore...
だから
therefore...
やめらんねーよ やめらんねーよ ペコチキン
Can't stop, can't stop eating Peko Chicken!
とんでもねーよ とんでもねーよ ペコチキン
Incredible, incredible Peko Chicken!
パリっとジュワっとホロッと たっぷりアツアツ
Crisp, juicy, tender, piping hot!
ほらもう一つどうでしょう？
Here, how about another one?
冷めちゃヤダ 冷めちゃヤダ ペコチキン
Don't let it get cold, don't let it get cold, Peko Chicken!
あっためなきゃ あっためなきゃ ペコチキン
Gotta warm it up, gotta warm it up, Peko Chicken!
ガブっとバリっとクラっと にんまりぺろり
Chomp, crunch, dizzy with delight, grinning as I devour it!
おかしくなっちゃう美味しさ
A deliciousness that drives you wild!
めっちゃお届け
Delivering so much!
すっごいお届け
Delivering immensely!
お待たせペコ！
Sorry to keep you waiting, peko!
今夜は一緒にペコチキン
Tonight, let's enjoy Peko Chicken together!
ジューシーバリバリ ジューシーバリバリ
Juicy and crispy, juicy and crispy!
いらっしゃいませ いらっしゃいませ
Welcome, welcome!
さぁさぁ今日も元気に焼いて焼いて焼いちゃって
Come on, today again, lively frying, frying, frying away!
ぼっち様 幹事様 お一人飛んでパーティー様
For solo guests, party planners, lone flyers, and party crowds!
どうでしょう一つ ペコチキン
How about one Peko Chicken?
バカタレサーカス 参上！
Bakatare Circus is here!
じゃ行くよー！
Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set, go!
Are you ready Four! Ageteke Foo!!
Are you ready Four! Turn it up, Foo!!
超弩級のバカのお出まし！
The super-dreadnought fools are here!
Are you ready Four! Ageteke Foo!!
Are you ready Four! Turn it up, Foo!!
宴の合図 叫びましょう！
It's time for the banquet signal, let's shout!
Yeah!!!!
みんな、お待たせー！
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
我々の出番だー！
It's our turn now!
最高に盛り上げていくから
We're gonna pump this up to the max,
楽しんでいこう！
so enjoy it!
始まるよ suddenly
It begins suddenly,
思い立ったら nice day! (nice day!)
the moment you feel like it, it's a nice day! (nice day!)
ノープランでも駆け抜けろ (oh oh oh)
Even with no plan, run straight through! (oh oh oh)
遊び疲れたら
When you get tired from playing around,
温かなお茶で break time (break time)
take a break with a warm cup of tea (break time).
メリハリつけて楽しみ尽くそう
Keep the balance and enjoy it to the fullest!
好奇心は止まらない
Curiosity won't stop,
どんなストーリーが待っているかな
wonder what kind of story is waiting for us?
Are you ready Four! Ageteke Foo!!
Are you ready Four! Turn it up, Foo!!
バカなこと起こすお祭りだ
It's a festival for doing silly things!
make it loud この瞬間をバカ騒ごう
Make it loud! Let me hear you get crazy right now!
ハチャメチャ劇ノリが大事 遠慮なんていらないよ
A wild, energetic vibe is key, no need to hold back!
one two jump 果てしなく飛べ 思いのまま
One, two, jump! Fly endlessly, just as you wish!
青春とは刹那的さ
Youth is just fleeting,
楽しむしかないじゃん
so all you can do is enjoy it!
不揃いなままで通じ合う
Even unmatched, we understand each other—
私たちが best friends!
we are best friends!
ハイ！
Hey!
一番デカい声出せ (go go!)
Shout with your loudest voice! (go go!)
またとないこの機会を (go go!)
This once-in-a-lifetime chance, (go go!)
とんでもねぇ、待ってたんだ (go go!)
heck yeah, we've been waiting for this! (go go!)
やいのやいの愛も変わんない！
All this chaotic love hasn't changed a bit!
まだまだ声出せるよね！いっそー！
You can still shout louder, right?! Let's go even further!
せーの！
Ready, set!
Are you ready Four! Ageteke Foo!!
Are you ready Four! Turn it up, Foo!!
バカなこと起こすお祭りだ
It's a festival for doing silly things!
vivid な stampede 集まり超 laugh in
A vivid stampede gathering, super laughing in!
最高潮な時間をほら gimme gimme more!
Give me, give me more of this climax time!
nobody's fool! みんなで叫ぼうぜ
Nobody's fool! Let's shout together!
愛込めて せーの “bakatare circus!!!!”
With love, ready, set: "Bakatare Circus!!!!"
好奇心は終わらない
Curiosity never ends,
どんなストーリーが待っているかな
wonder what kind of story is waiting for us?
大切なこの瞬間を分かち合おう
Let's share this precious moment!
紡いできた思い出をさ 飾り付けて さぁ
Let me decorate the memories we've woven together, come on!
make it loud この瞬間をバカ騒ごう
Make it loud! Let me hear you get crazy right now!
ハチャメチャ劇ノリが大事 遠慮なんていらないよ
A wild, energetic vibe is key, no need to hold back!
one two jump 果てしなく飛べ 思いのまま
One, two, jump! Fly endlessly, just as you wish!
青春とは刹那的さ
Youth is just fleeting,
楽しむしかないじゃん
so all you can do is enjoy it!
がむしゃらがずっとお似合いさ
Going all out has always suited us best!
私たちはまだはしゃぐよ hands up!!!!
We're still gonna fool around, hands up!!!!
Lalalalala...
Yeah!!!!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
みんなありがとー！
Thank you, everyone!
このあともたくさん盛り上がってねー！
Keep having an amazing time for the rest of the show~!
以上、バカタレサーカスの楽曲でした！ありがとうございました！
That was Bakatare Circus's song! Thank you so much!
ありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much~!
最高！最高！
Awesome! Awesome!
やりきったね今日も！
We gave it our all today too!
まだまだ ... まだ始まったばかり！
It's only just begun!
ということでちょっとね、皆さん
So, everyone!
コールアンドレスポンスもしたいと思いますので
I was thinking I'd like to do a call and response too,
自己紹介タイムやっていきましょうか！
so shall we do our introduction time?
はい！白上フブキ！
Okay! Shirakami Fubuki!
「コンコンきつね」って言ったら「コンコンきつね」で返してください
When I say "Konkon Kitsune", please reply with "Konkon Kitsune".
いけますか？　ーいけます！　ーはい、では行きますよー！
Are you ready? —Ready! —Okay, here we go!
皆さん！コンコンきつねー！
Everyone! Konkon Kitsune!
コンコンきつねー！
Konkon Kitsune!
あ、あれもやっておくか
Ah, should I do that one too?
フワフワしっぽの五目煮！
Fluffy tail gomokuni!
あなたの心の一番星！
The number one star in your heart!
白上フブキです！ Hi friends! How are you?
I'm Shirakami Fubuki! Hi friends! How are you?
まあフェスだからね、やっておきましょう。じゃあ次ね！
Well, since it's a festival, let's do it. Next up!
私「ハイダーリン」って言ったら「ハイダーリン」って返してください！
When I say "Hi Darling", please reply with "Hi Darling"!
「世界で一番」って聞くんで、「愛してる」って返してください！
And when I ask "Who's number one in the world?", reply with "I love you"!
オッケー？行きますよー！ハイダーリン！
Okay? Here we go! Hi Darling!
ハイダーリン！
Hi Darling!
世界で一番？
Who's number one in the world?
愛してる！
I love you!
ありがとうございます！ホロライブ3期生、不知火フレアです！
Thank you very much! I'm Shiranui Flare from Hololive 3rd Gen!
次、わためぇちゃんかな？
Next up, Watame-chan?
みんなわかるよね？　ーお？なんだろう？
Everyone knows, right? —Oh? What could it be?
ホロライブ4期生、角巻…え？わためー！
Hololive 4th Gen, Tsunomaki... Huh? Watame!
わためー！
Watame!
ちょっと待って、それ「ジャンケン」じゃない？
Wait a minute, isn't that wrong?
角巻…わためー！
Tsunomaki... Watame!
わためー！
Watame!
わためナンバーワン！
Watame Number One!
ふりが雑！雑でいいの？
That intro was so lazy! Is being lazy okay?
あ、ドドドドド！
Ah, Dododododo!
ホロライブ4期生、角巻わためです！
I'm Tsunomaki Watame from Hololive 4th Gen!
ね、思ったんだけど、あれじゃないの今のは？
Hey, I was thinking, wasn't that a bit off just now?
わためのコーレスはさ、「こんばん…ドドド」だと思って…
I thought Watame's call and response was "Konban... Dododo"...
いつもの挨拶忘れるなよ！　ーごめん！
Don't forget your usual greeting! —Sorry!
「ポルカおるかー？」って言ったら「おるよー！」って言ってほしいな！
When I say "Is Polka here?", I want you to say "I'm here!"!
行くよー！ポルカ、おるかー？
Here we go! Is Polka here?
おるよー！
I'm here!
ホロライブ5期生ねぽらぼの尾丸ポルカです！よろしくお願いします！
I'm Omaru Polka from Hololive 5th Gen Nepolabo! Pleased to meet you!
すごい、温まってる！いい、いいねー！
Awesome, the crowd is warmed up! Nice, nice!
みんな声出出てる感じですか、ポルカさん？
Do you feel like everyone is shouting out loud, Polka-san?
いやーね、まだ足りないよ、声がちょっとみんな！
No way, everyone's voice is still not enough!
まだ行けるよな！始まったばっかりだもんな！
We can still go! We've only just started!
「盛り上がってるかー？」って聞くんで、「ウワー！」とか言ってください！
When I ask "Are you hyped?", please say "Woah!" or something!
いくよみんな、せーの！盛り上がってるかー？
Here we go everyone, 1, 2! Are you hyped up?!
イエーイ！
Yeah!
すごーい！声でてる！
Awesome! Great voices!
あれもやろうよ、名物！ウェーブ作ろう！
Let's do that signature thing too! Let's make a wave!
じゃあこっちからウェーブいきますよー！
Alright, wave starting from this side, here it goes!
ペンライト振って、手でもいいよ！いくよー！出航！
Wave your penlights or hands! Here we go! Set sail!
すげー！上手く出来ました！
Awesome! That went so well!
改めましてCapture the Momentが始まりました！そして初挑戦、みんな！
Once again, Capture the Moment has begun! And our first try, everyone!
トロッコ見てくれましたかー？！
Did you see the parade floats?!
見たー！
We saw them!
いつもより近くに我々のこと見れた方々がいっぱいいるんじゃないでしょうか！
There must be so many people who got to see us closer than usual!
どうだったー？　ーよかったー！　ーありがとうございます！
How was it? —It was great! —Thank you so much!
帰宅してからでもいいですし、配信見ている方はぜひハッシュタグ…
Even after returning home, or for those watching the stream, please use the hashtag...
#hololiveFesEXPO24Day1 で本日感想などよろしくお願いします！
#hololiveFesEXPO24Day1 today, and share your thoughts and feedback!
そしてなんと…え？あ、早い早い早い！
And what's more... Huh? Ah, fast, fast, fast!
そして、無料配信でご覧の方々はなんと…
And for those watching via free stream, surprisingly...
ここまでー！
It ends here!
えー！まだまだ見たいですよねー！
Eh?! You want to watch more, right?!
概要欄から配信サイトに行ってチケット、よろしくお願いします！
Head over to the streaming site from the description box and grab your tickets!
お願いします！絶対見てね！
Please do! Be sure to check it out!
まあ我々もですね、ユニット曲は終わってしまったんですけどソロ曲もありますからね！
Well, as for us, though our unit songs are done, we still have solo performances coming up!
この場をお借りして
Taking this opportunity,
まあ、よければさ
well, if you'd like,
みんなソロ曲のときに
during everyone's solo songs,
ファンのみんなに何してほしいかっていうのを
what you'd like the fans to do...
リクエストありますかね？
Are there any requests?
サイリウムの...
Like penlight...
ペンライトの色、何色がいいとかさ
What color penlight you'd prefer, and so on...
オレンジがいい！
Orange is good!
えー！ オレンジ！？ え、嘘ー！？
Eh! Orange!? Wait, really!?
え、でも、なんか... 違うのか？
Eh, but wait... Is that not it?
曲に合わせてこう手拍子があったら...
If everyone claps along to the song...
エモい感じにしてもらったりとかしてほしいな！
I'd love it if you made it feel emotional!
おー、いいですね！
Oh, that sounds great!
わためは？
What about Watame?
え？
Eh?
やっぱ一番でかい声を！
Definitely the loudest cheer!
出してほしいなと思って！
I want you to shout as loud as you can!
でかい声！
Loud voice!
でかい声出せるよなー！？
You can shout really loud, right!?
でかい声ー！
Loud voice!
出せるよなー！
You can do it, right!?
わためのソロ曲のときもよろしくお願いします！
Please show that energy during Watame's solo song too!
そしてポルカはどうですか？
And how about Polka?
もちろん盛り上がってくれるよねー！
Of course you'll get super hyped, right!?
おー！
Woah!
ポルカのときもよろしくお願いします！
Please give it your all for Polka too!
そうですね！ 白上ちょっとあの...
That's right! As for Shirakami...
ペンライトに触れたんですけど...
I touched on penlights earlier...
白上のソロ曲のときはぜひとも皆さん...
During Shirakami's solo song, please, everyone...
白上のカラーではなく、皆さんの最推しのカラーで...
use the color of your ultimate favorite idol, not Shirakami's color...
ええー！？
Ehhh!?
マジか！
Seriously!?
迷った方は白とか青でもいいですけど...
If you're unsure, white or blue is fine, but...
まぁ今回のね、Day 1...
Well, for Day 1...
含めホロライブプロダクションに好きな推しのカラーが皆さんのあると思います！
including all of Hololive Production, I'm sure everyone has a favorite idol color!
白上のソロ曲のときはぜひとも皆さんの最推しのカラーで...
So during Shirakami's solo song, please use your absolute favorite's color...
えー！
Woah!
振ってくれると...
If you wave those...
多分すごーい良い景色になるんじゃないかと思ってます！
I think it will create a truly amazing view!
白上のソロ曲もお願いします！
So please support Shirakami's solo song as well!
お願いします！
Please do!
さあ、じゃあ配信のみんなが見てる...
Now then, for everyone watching on the stream...
うらやましい感じでみんなで「イエーイ」って言ったり配信のみんなに...
Let's make them envious by shouting "Yay!" together to all the stream viewers...
イエーイ！
Yay!
この後も盛り上がっていくぞー！
Let's keep the energy going!
イエーイ！
Yay!
さあ、続いての楽曲も準備できてるっぽいのでね！
Now then, it looks like the next song is ready!
いけますか？
Are we ready?
行きますか！ じゃあ...
Let's go then! So...
今回皆さん「Ridin' on Dreams」がテーマなので...
Since "Ridin' on Dreams" is our theme this time...
これで締めたいと思います！ 行きますよ！
We'd like to end with this! Here we go!
せーの！
Ready, set...
Ridin' on Dreams!
無料パートは終了いたしました！ ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The sneak peek part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!